#### Contact

2603011738 (Mobile) trentonlkirchner@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/trenton-kirchner-91b38b174 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Customer Relationship Management (CRM)

Customer Service Sales

# Trenton Kirchner

#### Student

Nashville Metropolitan Area

### Summary

Hi, my name is Trenton Kirchner and I'm a 26-year-old emerging full stack developer from northern Indiana, currently living in Nashville. I am new to the field and am excited to continue growing my skills. Before pursuing a career in tech, I worked in sales and customer service, which taught me the importance of attention to detail and problem-solving. I'm committed to the quality of my work and take pride in writing clean, efficient, and maintainable code.I graduated from Vanderbilts Full Stack bootcamp with a certificate for coding and have been honing my skills ever since. I believe in treating everyone fairly while maintaining a level of reachable expectations. I'm eager to help and always open to new opportunities to learn and grow. When I'm not coding, I enjoy paddle boarding, working on my bus, and hiking. Thank you for taking the time to read my bio, and I look forward to connecting with you!

## Experience

Warby Parker Customer Success Specialist November 2020 - November 2022 (2 years 1 month) Nashville, Tennessee, United States

Hallmark Volkswagen
Sales Associate
June 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 4 months)
Franklin Tennessee

Zumiez Store Manager October 2016 - March 2019 (2 years 6 months)

Pizza Hut Delivery Driver January 2016 - January 2018 (2 years 1 month)

Page 1 of 2

Decatur, Indiana

Being a delivery driver I was trusted to assure each product was brought to a customers door in a timely manner with no imperfections.

Kroger

Gas Station Cashier June 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 8 months) Decatur, Indiana

As the gas station cashier I was responsible for completing transactions, restocking product, maintaining a clean and safe environment for all patrons, and problem solving.

### Education

Bellmont Senior High School core 40 · (2011 - 2015)

Vanderbilt University Boot Camps